<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Longread on Claire Parker-Jones Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/longread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Longread on Claire Parker-Jones Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 20:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/longread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A 101 day GitHub streak</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2016-04-10-a-101-day-github-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 20:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2016-04-10-a-101-day-github-streak/</guid>
      <description>📆 I was going to call this post &amp;ldquo;101 days of coding&amp;rdquo;, but that would be misleading. I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting paid to write code as a web developer for over 2 years now, but over the past 3+ months I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing code in my spare time - after work, after chores, after slobbing in front of the TV - and then committing and pushing it to GitHub. The really weird and pointless thing about this is that I&amp;rsquo;ve done it every day since the 1st of January this year and now I have a pretty good streak, just look at my GitHub scorecard:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding After Codecademy</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2015-11-03-coding-after-codecademy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2015-11-03-coding-after-codecademy/</guid>
      <description>Last month, I gave a lightning talk called &amp;ldquo;Coding After Codecademy&amp;rdquo; which was inspired by people asking me how to improve their newly acquired web development skills, now they&amp;rsquo;ve completed some Codecademy/Udacity/Code School courses. They&amp;rsquo;ve got basic HTML, CSS and JavaScript syntax, so what are some good things to start building or learning next? I know how daunting it can be to be faced with a blank editor at that stage, so in my talk I gave some common-sense advice that I would have appreciated when I was in that position myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LeedsHack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2015-09-14-leedshack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 22:14:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2015-09-14-leedshack/</guid>
      <description>Or, what to expect at a hack I went to my first hack a couple of weeks ago and wanted to (belatedly) share with you my experience and maybe even convince you to go to one yourself!
LeedsHack was held in Leeds City Museum on Saturday 22nd and Sunday 23rd August. The aim of the game was to create a demoable project or hack in just 24 hours, with coding starting at 12pm on Saturday and finishing at noon on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pomodoros &amp; Pair Programming</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2015-09-01-pomodoros-and-pair-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 23:00:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2015-09-01-pomodoros-and-pair-programming/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR  Next time you pair program, try using the Pomodoro Technique to improve your productivity and mix things up a bit. Breaks up difficult or tedious stories Keeps morale high and dev&#39;s brains fresh Time box learning or research which is sometimes easier to do solo Not always possible - everything in moderation   I currently work in a team where we pair program most of the time, and I&amp;rsquo;ve found that applying the principles of the Pomodoro Technique to when pairing - focus for a bit then a short break - has helped me work more effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>